relevance.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy - Relevance

We are presenting the details of our Privacy Policy, which include details of the type of information we collect and how it is usually utilized. We always make sure that privacy of our users is fully protected whichever way we utilize the information garnered.

This document details the various terms and conditions between us (Relevance) and you (the user of our services). Please read the document listing the terms and conditions very carefully. Also, note that we reserve the right to make changes to the below mentioned terms and conditions as and when deemed necessary. However, any such changes will be communicated to our users by mentioning them on our website. The current document of terms and conditions is in effect from March 2017.

This notice is applicable to all the information collected or submitted on the Relevance website.

**Links To Third Parties:**

Relevance websites are free to include links to third parties. Such links can be in the form of branded content, sponsored newsletters, advertisements, or any such form of content. Neither will be we be held responsible, nor are we liable for the manner in which third parties handle content, such as personal information, when our users visit or browse through their website. We make sure that our website users are fully aware of this fact.

**Use Of Personal Data:**

We reserve the right to contact you with content that is commercial or editorial in nature when you sign up for or show your intent to participate in one or more than one of the services mentioned below. Such communication will be done through email or instant messages if you provide us a contact number.

  * Signing up for our newsletter
  * Signing up for any of our events
  * Participating in any surveys conducted by us

Please note that we use our email list for secured communication with all our partners.

Relevance will never share your personal information provided to us or use it in any way except for the ones that we have stated. We always provide you the opportunity to opt out from our emailing list. You can also prevent us from using your personal information for reasons other than intended.

Relevance also states that we will not give away any personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information, or other types of personal information to any third party without your clear and explicit consent.

You can voluntarily give us your permission to collect and store data of the below-mentioned types for purposes of internal use:

  * Mandatory and voluntary data collected while signing up for subscription
  * Disclosing personal information voluntarily while taking part in our online surveys

If you have chosen to receive any communication through email about any programs or events, or communication about related events, Relevance may utilize such data with the intent of communicating with you on specific topics that you have shown interest in.

If you have provided us your contact/mobile number, it is assumed that you agree to any receiving any communication by us through text messages for any event/program that we are conducting.

It is also assumed that you agree to a deeper analysis of the personal data you have shared with us for the purpose of scoring or advertising. However, we intent to clarify that your email address will be used for any such purpose only with your clear and express consent.

By sharing your personal details and contact details with us, you also give us consent for updating and supplementing your data with additional data.

It also means that your consent has been received to collect your personal information from any public domain sources and for storing this data along with your personal data that is already available with us. You agree to allow us the use of the same for communications on topics of interest to you, such as program and events that are organized by Relevance from time to time.

**Personal Information:**

Most of the times, all personal information such as name, address of work place, email address, phone numbers and other contact details are provided through our official website or communicated to us directly by email.

However, it is assumed that we have your consent for:

  * Processing and administering the personal data shared with us to carry out specific and necessary actions so that your request or instructions can be completed or complied with.
  * Maintaining and retaining a record of all communication (incoming and outgoing) with the intention of processing your personal data.

**We might also collect the following details from you as a part of our Privacy Policy:**

  * Information provided at the time of filling in forms on our website
  * Your name and physical address for contacting you, for shipping, and for collection of payment
  * Email ID and contact numbers
  * Information related to your debit/credit card and bank accounts
  * Date of birth
  * Tax related numbers, PIN, or any other number related to tax records

We might maintain a record of correspondence generated when you contact us. The information we receive from credit reference and fraud detection agencies or any other third party for the purpose of verifying information shared with us during such communication will be kept in our records. We may also request you to participate in surveys, research tasks, and similar exercises, although the participation is entirely voluntary and you are free to not respond to such requests.

We will also keep a record of your personal choices and preferences indicated to us during various types of communications. We shall also retain data shared with us through third parties such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, and other channels via correspondence, writings, comments, blogs, photos, testimonials, customer care communications, surveys, and others.

User information can generally be included as part of a transaction in the event of total or partial acquisition of the organization by a third party of the NAI. This is also applicable in the event of Relevance shutting shop or filing for bankruptcy. By using our services, you give consent for your information to be used by any such acquiring company or entity.

**Cookies**

This website makes use of cookies. They are small text files that are placed on your machine with the intention of providing users of the website a better experience and also to create targeted advertising.

Cookies have been designed to enhance your browsing experience. However, you are free to disable cookies on this website. The best way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. NAI and its collaborators will treat this information confidentially.

**Rights of Access**

You have a right to demand a copy of any of your personal data held by Relevance. You can request for the same by sending out en email to our concerned executive.

**Right Of Rectification Or Deletion:**

If you are of the opinion that Relevance is in possession of information that’s inaccurate or incorrect which was submitted by you through our website, then you are well within your right to request for amendment of the data. You can also ask for deletion of any data or information shared with us through the website. To request for information rectification or deletion, please email to us, stating the details. The email must also include your address and a brief description of the specific data that needs to be changed or removed.

Please note that we are not specifically required to change or remove any data or information if such changes and deletions will affect the status of your contractual obligations with us in any way.

We request you to ensure that data provided is accurate. We have systems in place to prevent any illegal or unauthorized access to your data. At our end, we take extreme care to maintain data accuracy and make sure that the information provided to us is used in the appropriate manner.
